Picture Collection LSC.0099.a
UCLA Library Special Collections
Picture collection
1890-
UCLA Library Special Collections
LSC.0099.a
40.8 Linear Feet (95 boxes and 14 flat boxes)
The collection consists of original 19th and 20th century photographs and reproductions covering a broad range of subjects as well as a small collection of original artwork. Subjects in the collection include: Los Angeles, Hollywood, Pasadena, California missions, adobes, and ranchos, the U.S. Civil War, and Latin America. Includes portraits, landscapes, cityscapes, panoramic views, location shots, and more.
Conditions Governing Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance through our electronic paging system using the request button located on this page.
Portions of collection held at SRLF. Portions of collection held on-site at UCLA Library Special Collections.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 4233586
Scope and Content
Collection consists of original and copy 19th and 20th century photographs covering a broad range of subjects including, Los Angeles California, Hollywood California, Pasadena California, California missions, adobes, and ranchos, the U.S. civil war, and Latin America. Includes portraits, landscapes, cityscapes, panoramic views, location shots, and more. Also includes a small collection of original art work.
Related Material
Photographers Collection (Collection 98). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections.
Landscape photographs.; Photographs -- 19th century.; Panoramic photographs.; Portrait photographs.; Photographs -- 20th century.; Cityscape photographs.
- Abzug, Bella S. -- Portrait. (Box 108, Folder 1)
- Accounting Machines -- Views. (Box 108, Folder 2)
- Acri. (Folder 3)
- Adams, Ansel Easton, 1902-1984, -- Portrait. (Folder 4)
- Adams, Calif. -- Views. (Folder 8)
- Adams, Charles Francis, 1807-1886. (Box 108, Folder 5)
- Adams, John Quincy, pres. U.S., 1767-1848, -- Portrait. (Box 108, Folder 7)
- Adams, John, pres. U.S., 1735-1826. (Box 108, Folder 6)
- Ade, George, 1866-1944. (Box 108, Folder 9)
- Adobes - Calif., *ALSO SHELVED* (Box 108, Folder 10)
- Adobes - Calif. - Aguilar Adobe, San Juan Capistrano. (Box 108, Folder 11)
- Adobes - Calif. - Avila (Francis) Adobe, Los Angeles -- Views. (Box 108, Folder 12)
- Adobes - Calif. - Casa Adobe (Southwest Museum), Los Angeles. (Box 108, Folder 15)
- Adobes - Calif. - Casa Adobe de San Rafael, Gendale. (Folder 14)
- Adobes - Calif. - Castro Adobe, San Juan Bautista. (Box 108, Folder 13)
- Adobes - Calif. - Coronel (Ygnacio) Adobe, Los Angeles. (Box 108, Folder 16)
- Adobes - Calif. - De La Guerre Adobe, Santa Barbara -- Views. (Box 108, Folder 17)
- Adobes - Calif. - Howard (Volney E.) Adobe, San Gabriel. (Folder 18)
- Adobes - Calif. - Lugo (Vicente) Adobe, Los Angeles -- Views. (Box 108, Folder 19)
- Adobes - Calif. - Lugo, (Jose Antonio) Adobe, Los Angeles -- Views. (Box 108, Folder 20)
- Adobes - Calif. - Mahoney (J.C.) Adobe, San Miguel, Calif. (Folder 21)
- Adobes - Calif. - Rios (Petronilo) Adobe, San Miguel, Calif. (Box 108, Folder 22)
- Adobes - Calif. - Ruis (Mariano) Adobe, Los Angeles -- Views. (Box 108, Folder 27)
- Adobes - Calif. - Sanchez (Vicente) Adobe, Los Angeles. (Box 108, Folder 23)
- Adobes - Calif. - Sepulveda (Enrique) Adobe, Los Angles. (Folder 24)
- Adobes - Calif. - Sonoratown Adobe, Los Angeles -- Views. (Box 108, Folder 25)
- Adobes - Calif. - Thompson (Alpheus) Adobe, Santa Barbara. (Box 108, Folder 26)
- Adobes - Calif. - Ybarra (Pedro) Adobe, Los Angeles. (Box 108, Folder 28)
- Adobes- California - Lugo Adobe, Los Angeles., 1 item (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Aeronautics -- Views. (folder 1 of 3) (Box 108, Folder 29)
- Aeronautics -- Views. (folder 2 of 3) (Box 108, Folder 30)
- Aeronautics -- Views. (folder 3 of 3) (Box 108, Folder 31)
- Aeroplane Industry and Trade - Calif. -- Views. (Box 108, Folder 32)
- Africans -- Portraits., 3 items (Folder 7)
- Afton, Calif. -- Views. (Folder 1)
- Agassiz, Jean Louis Rodolphe, 1807-1873. (Folder 2)
- Agricultural Machinery -- Views. (folder 1 of 2), *ALSO SHELVED* (Box 109, Folder 4)
- Agricultural Machinery -- Views. (folder 2 of 2) (Box 109, Folder 5)
- Agriculture - Calif., *AlSO SHELVED* (Folder 3)
- Agriculture, California. (folder 1 of 3), 27 items (Folder 1)
- Agriculture, California. (folder 2 of 3), 6 items (Folder 2)
- Agriculture, California. (folder 3 of 3) (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Agua Mansa Cemetary, San Bernardino County, Calif. (Box 109, Folder 6)
- Aguilar Family. (Folder 7)
- Aguinaldo y Famy, Emilio, 1869-1964, -- Portrait. (Folder 8)
- Aide, Hamilton, 1826-1906, -- Portrait. (Folder 9)
- Ainsworth, William Harrison. (Box 109, Folder 10)
- Alabama Hills. (Box 109, Folder 11)
- Alameda, Calif. -- Views. (Folder 12)
- Alamogordo, N.M. -- Views. (Folder 13)
- Alaska -- Views. (folder 1 of 2) (Folder 14)
- Alaska -- Views. (folder 2 of 2) (Box 109, Folder 15)
- Albert I, king of the Belgians, 1875-1934. (Box 109, Folder 16)
- Albion, Calif. -- Views. (Folder 17)
- Albright, Horace Marden, 1890-1987, -- Portrait., 3 items (Folder 1)
- Albuquerque, New Mexico., 33 items (Folder 2)
- Alcatraz Island, Calif. -- Views. (Box 109, Folder 18)
- Alcott, Carrol, 1901-1965., 2 items (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Aldine Academy, Venice., 2 items (Folder 3)
- Aldington, Richard, 1892-1962., 4 items (Folder 4)
- Aldrich, Mark A., 1 item (Folder 5)
- Aldrich, Winthrop William, 1885-1974., 1 item (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Alexander, David W., 1 item (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Alford, Charles H., 1 item (Folder 8)
- Algeria -- Views., 3 items (Folder 9)
- Alhambra., 8 items (Folder 10)
- Allen, George., 1 item (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Allen, Grant, 1848-1899, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Allen, John B., 1 item (Folder 13)
- Allensworth, Allen, 1842-1914., 1 item (Folder 14)
- Altadena -- Views., 2 items (Folder 15)
- Althouse, D. T., 1 item (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Altmeyer, Arthur Joseph, 1891-1972., 1 item (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Alto, Gertrude., 1 item (Folder 18)
- Alvarado Family -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 19)
- American Library Association, Annual Conference, Los Angeles, 1953., 105 items (Box 1, Folder 20)
  General note
  ALSO: *
- American Library Association. Annual Conference -- Views., 2 items (Box 101, Folder 1)
- American Medical Association, Los Angeles., 2 items (Box 1, Folder 21)
- American River, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Anacapa Islands -- Views., 10 items (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Anaheim, Calif. -- Views., 62 items (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Ancient & Honorable Order of E. Clampus Vitus -- Portraits., 2 items (Folder 25)
- Andrews, Edmund -- Portrait., 11 items (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Angel's Camp., 7 items (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Antelope Valley Siphon, California., 9 items (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Anthony, Charles Edward., 1 item (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Anthony, Edward A. -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 30)
- Anthony, Henry T. -- Portrait., 3 items (Folder 31)
- Anthony, Susan Brownell, 1820-1906., 1 item (Folder 32)
- Antwerp, Musee Plantin-Moretus., 6 items (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Apparitions -- Views., 9 items (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Arabia -- Views., 24 items (Folder 35)
- Arblay, Frances (Burney) d', 1752-1840., 1 item (Folder 36)
- Arbogast, F., 1 item (Folder 37)
- Arcadia., 2 items (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Architecture, Domestic -- Views (California, Southern)., 4 items (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Architecture, Domestic -- Views., 52 items (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Architecture, France -- Views (Chateaux)., 3 items (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Architecture, Spain -- Views., 2 items (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Arguello, Luis Antonio -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Arizona., 54 items (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Arlington, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Armenia -- Views., 33 items (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Arms and Armour -- Views., 22 items (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Armstrong, Martin Donisthorpe, 1882-1974., 1 item (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Arnold, Henry Harley, 1886-1950., 1 item (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Arnold, Mathew, 1822-1888, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 12)
- Arrowhead Hot Spring, Calif., 9 items (Folder 13)
- Arrowhead, Lake -- Views., 21 items (Folder 14)
- Art, African., 18 items (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Artesia, N.M. -- Views., 19 items (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Asilomar, Calif. -- Views., 11 items (Folder 17)
- Aspen, Colo., 28 items (Folder 18)
- Astronomical Observations., 9 items (Folder 19)
- Atascadero, Calif. -- Views., 16 items (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Atherton, Gertrude Franklin (Horn), 1857-1948., 1 item (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Auburn., 5 items (Folder 22)
- Aurora, Nevada., 7 items (Folder 23)
- Ausable Chasm, New York -- Views., 2 items (Folder 24)
- Austin, Alexander M., 1826- -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Austin, John Conneley Wilson, 1870-1963, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Austin, Mary (Hunter) 1868-1934., 8 items (Folder 27)
- Austin, Texas -- Views., 6 items (Folder 28)
- Australia -- Views (Folder 1 of 3)., 13 items (Folder 1)
- Australia -- Views (Folder 2 of 3)., 69 items (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Australia -- Views (Folder 3 of 3)., 57 items (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Automobiles -- Views (Folder 1 of 2)., 61 items (Folder 4)
- Automobiles -- Views (Folder 2 of 2)., 200 items (Folder 5)
- Avery, Ira -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 1)
- Avila Family -- Portrait., 10 items (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Aztec Ruins National Monument, N.M. -- Views., 4 items (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Aztec, N.M. -- Views., 16 items (Folder 3)
- Azusa, Calif., 13 items (Folder 5)
- Bagehot, Walter, 1826-1877 -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 6)
- Baker, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Baker, James Marion, 1861-1940, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Baker, Mount (Wash.) -- Views., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Bakersfield, Calif., 4 items (Folder 10)
- Baldwin, Anita., 1 item (Folder 11)
- Baldwin, Elias Jackson, 1828-1903, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Ball, B. F., 6 items (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Balloon Route Excursion Co. (Los Angeles, Calif.), 1 item (Folder 14)
- Ballooning - California., 1 item (Folder 15)
- Bancroft, Hubert Howe, 1832-1918, -- Portraits., 4 items (Folder 16)
- Bandini Family -- Portrait., 11 items (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Bands (Music) -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Bank buildings., 2 items (Folder 19)
- Banning, Calif. -- Views., 6 items (Folder 20)
- Banning, Lucy Tichnor, 1876-1929, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 21)
- Banning, Phineas., 9 items (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Barkley, Alben William, 1877-1956., 1 item (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Barrows, Henry Dwight, 1825-1914., 1 item (Folder 24)
- Barstow, California -- Views., 34 items (Folder 25)
- Baruch (Herbert M.) Corporation, Ltd., Los Angeles. (Folder 26)
  Filed in separate drawer at end of Picture Collection
- Baths -- Views (Folder 1 of 2)., 11 items (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Baths -- Views (Folder 2 of 2)., 32 items (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Baum, Vicki, 1888-1960, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 29)
- Beaconsfield, Benjamin Disraeli., 6 items (Folder 30)
- Bear Valley, Mariposa Co., Calif., 1 item (Folder 31)
- Beaudry, Prudent., 2 items (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Beaumont, William, 1785-1853., 1 item (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Beauregard, Pierre Gustave Toutant, 1818-1893, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 34)
- Beck, Frederick K. -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Becker, Thilo., 1 item (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Beecher, Henry Ward, 1813-1887, -- Portrait., 5 items (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Belen, N.M. -- Views., 4 items (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Bell Family -- Portrait., 10 items (Folder 41)
- Bell Ranch, New Mexico. Last frontiersman. Exhibit of UCLA Library, June, 1957, of 9 photographs by Robert M. Billow, showing life at the Bell Ranch, 1928-1929., 10 items (Folder 1)
- Bell, Alexander Graham, 1847-1922, -- Portrait., 9 items (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Bell, Alphonzo Edward, 1875-1947., 5 items (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Bellini, Vincenso, 1806-1835, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 2)
- Bence, G. W., 1 item (Folder 3)
- Benchley, Robert Charles, 1889-1945, -- Portrait., 2 items (Folder 4)
- Benedict, Sir Julius, 1805-1885, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Benguet (Philippines: Province)., 25 items (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Bennett, Raphael Fabian, 1895-1957., 6 items (Folder 7)
- Benson, Edward Frederick, 1867-1940., 2 items (Folder 8)
- Beranger, Pierre Jean De., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Bergin, John J. -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Berkeley, Calif., 47 items (Box 5, Folder 11)
  ALSO SHELVED*
- Berkeley, Calif. -- Views. (Box 100, Folder 2)
- Berle, Adolf Augustus, 1895-1971., 1 item (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Berlin., 38 items (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Bernard Family -- Portrait., 4 items (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Besant, Walter, 1836-1901., 1 item (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Beveridge, Albert Jeremiah, 1862-1927, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 16)
- Beveridge, Daeida Wilcox., 2 items (Folder 17)
- Beverly Hills, Calif., 22 items (Folder 18)
- Bible. Latin. ca. 1450-1455. Mainz, Gutenberg (42 lines) -- Views., 2 items (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Bickerdyke, Mary A. Ball., 1 item (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Bicycles and Tricycles., 3 items (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Biddle, Francis Beverly, 1886-1968., 1 item (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Bidwell Bar State Park, Calif. -- Views., 4 items (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Bidwell, Annie Kennedy., 1 item (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Biescar, H., 1 item (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Big Basin Redwoods State Park, Calif. -- Views., 6 items (Folder 26)
- Big Bear Lake, Calif. --Views., 14 items (Folder 27)
- Big Pines, Calif. --Views., 20 items (Folder 28)
- Big Sur, Calif. -- Views., 10 items (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Bilicke, Albert C., Family -- Portraits., 20 items (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Biscailuz, Eugene Warren, 1883-1969., 28 items (Folder 31)
- Bishop, Calif. -- Views., 3 items (Folder 32)
- Bismark, Otto, F?rst von, 1815-1898., 1 item (Folder 33)
- Bison, American., 1 item (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Bispham, David Scull, 1857-1921, -- Portrait., 3 items (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Bixby, Llewellyn, 1826?-1896., 6 items (Folder 36)
- Black, William, 1841-1898., 1 items (Folder 1)
- Blackfoot, Ida. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 2)
- Blackie, John Stuart, 1809-1895., 1 item (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Blacks in America -- Portraits., 1 item (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Blacksmithing -- Views., 5 items (Folder 5)
- Blackwood, Algernon, 1896-1951, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 6)
- Blairsden, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 7)
- Blanchard, Frederick Thomas, 1878-1946., 3 items (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Bland, Adam., 1 item (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Blasco Ib??ez, Vicente, 1867-1928, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 10)
- Bloom, Sol, 1870-1949., 1 item (Folder 11)
- Blue Canyon, Placer County, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Folder 12)
- Bodie, Calif., 6 items (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Boise, Ida. -- Views., 7 items (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Bond, Carrie Jacobs, 1862-1946., 3 items (Folder 15)
- Bonheur, Rosa, 1822-1899, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 16)
- Boni, Albert, 1892-1981, -- Portrait., 10 items (Folder 17)
- Bookbinding -- Specimens -- Views., 1 items (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Booth, John Wilkes, 1838-1865., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Borax Mines and Mining - California., 4 items (Folder 20)
- Borax Mule Teams., 2 items (Folder 21)
- Boron, Calif. -- Views., 1 items (Folder 22)
- Botillier Family -- Portrait., 3 items (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Bottello, Maclovio, 1856- -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Boulder, Colo. -- Views., 31 items (Folder 25)
- Bowen, William Miller, 1862-, 1 item (Folder 26)
- Bowles, Chester, 1901-1986, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 27)
- Bowles, Samuel, 1826-1878., 1 item (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Boyes Springs, Calif. -- Views., 3 items (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Bradely, Thomas, 1917-1998, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 31)
- Bradley, David, 1950- --Portrait., 1 item (Folder 30)
- Brawley, Calif. -- Views., 27 items (Folder 32)
- Brazil -- Views., 29 items (Box 97, Folder 4)
- Bremen., 2 items (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Brent, Joseph Lancaster., 2 items (Folder 34)
- Brereton, Lewis Hyde, 1890-1967., 1 item (Folder 35)
- Bridger Family -- Portrait., 3 items (Folder 36)
- Bridges -- Views., 11 items (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Brigham Young University, Provo, Utah -- Views., 3 items (Box 6, Folder 38)
- British Expeditionary Force in Abyssinia, 1868 -- Views., 69 items (Folder 39)
- Brodek, Janet Brown, collector., 11 items (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Broisat, Mlle. -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Bronte, Charlotte., 1 item (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Brookdale, Calif. -- Views., 12 items (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Brooks, Shirley, 1815-1874., 5 items (Folder 44)
- Brown Boys Rancho, Pasedena (?)., 1 item (Folder 50)
- Brown, Avery, 1852-, 2 items (Folder 45)
- Brown, Edmund G. 1905-1996., 1 item (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Brown, Jason., 1 item (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Brown, John, 1800-1859., 1 item (Folder 48)
- Brown, Prentiss Marsh, 1889-1973., 1 item (Folder 49)
- Browne, Charles Farrar, 1834-1867, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 1)
- Browne, John Ross, 1821-1875., 2 items (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Browne, Thomas Alexander, 1826-1915., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Browning, Robert, 1812-1889., 1 item (Folder 4)
- Bryan, William Jennings, 1860-1925., 4 items (Folder 5)
- Bryce Canyon Nation Monument -- Views., 2 items (Folder 6)
- Bryce Canyon National Park -- Views. (Box 100, Folder 3)
- Bryson Ranch, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Buchanan, Robert Williams, 1841-1901., 1 item (Folder 8)
- Bucks, Valley Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Buell, R. T., 2 items (Folder 10)
- Buena Vista Ranch, San Diego Co., Calif., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Buff, Conrad, 1886-1975, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Buffalo Bill., 21 items (Folder 13)
- Buffalo Creek Park, Colo. -- Views., 3 items (Folder 14)
- B?hlig, Richard, 1880-1952, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 15)
- Bull, Ole Borneman, 1810-1880, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Bunche, Ralf Johnson, 1904-1972, -- Portrait., 3 items (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Bundy, May Sutton., 3 items (Folder 18)
- Buonarroti, Michel Angelo, 1475-1564, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 19)
- Burbank, California -- Views., 2 items (Folder 20)
- Burbank, David., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Burbank, Luther, 1849-1926, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Burch, B. B., 1 item (Folder 23)
- Burch, Henry Kenyon, 1937-1957. (folder 1 of 2) (Folder 1)
- Burch, Henry Kenyon, 1937-1957. (folder 2 of 2) (Folder 2)
- Burcham, Charles A., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Burdett-Coutts, Angela Georgina Burdett-Coutts, baroness, 1814-1906., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Burdette, Robert Jones, 1844-1914., 2 items (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Burdick, Horace., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Burlingame, Calif., 2 items (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Burns, J. Frank., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Burroughs, Edgar Rice, 1875-1950., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Burroughs, John., 1 item (Folder 31)
- Burton, Harold Hitz, 1888-1964, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 32)
- Butler, Benjamin Franklin, 1818-1893., 1 item (Folder 33)
- Butte City., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Butterfield Trail -- Views., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Bynner, Witter, 1881-1968., 1 item (Folder 36)
- Bynum, Lindley, 1895-, 3 items (Folder 37)
- Byrd, Richard Evelyn, 1888-1957, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 38)
- Cabel, Marie, 1827-1885, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Cabell, James Branch, 1879-1958, -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Cabrillo, Juan Rodriquez, d. 1543, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 41)
- Cadam, Charles Wakefield, 1881-1946., 2 items (Folder 42)
- Caine, Sir Hall, 1853-1931., 1 item (Folder 43)
- Calame, Alexandre, 1810-1864., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Calaveras Big Trees State Park, Calif. -- Views., 4 items (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Calico, Calif. -- Views., 67 items (Folder 46)
- California -- Annexation to the U.S., 14 items (Folder 47)
- California - Views (Folder 1 of 2)., 40 items (Folder 53)
- California - Views (Folder 2 of 2)., 13 items (Box 7, Folder 54)
- California Development Company -- Views., 30 items (Folder 48)
- California Legislature - Senate -- Portrait., 1 item (Box 7, Folder 49)
- California State Normal School Faculty -- Portrait., 5 items (Box 7, Folder 51)
- California Volunteers -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 92, Folder 4)
- California, University of, Los Angeles. Library. Music Library - Exhibits -- Views., 4 items (Box 7, Folder 52)
- California. State Hospital, Camarillo -- Views., 3 items (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Calistoga, Calif. -- Views., 22 items (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Calles, Plutarco Elias., 1 item (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Camarillo, Adolfo., 1 item (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Cambria., 17 items (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Camp Baldy, Calif. -- Views., 13 items (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Campo, San Diego Co., California., 7 items (Folder 6)
- Canada -- Views., 90 items (Folder 7)
- Canals -- Views., 12 items (Folder 8)
- Canning, Lord., 1 item (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Cannon, Joseph Gurney, 1836-1926, -- Portrait., 15 items (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Canoga Park, California., 3 items (Folder 11)
- Canon City, Colo. -- Views., 14 items (Folder 12)
- Canyon de Chelley National Monument., 8 items (Folder 13)
- Canyon Diablo, Ariz., 2 items (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Cape Horn, Placer County, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Capitola, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 16)
- Carcour -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 42)
- Cardiff-by-the-Sea, Calif. -- Views, 2 items (Folder 17)
- Carlsbad, Calif. -- Views., 13 items (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Carlsbad, N.M. -- Views., 27 items (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Carlyle, Thomas., 4 items (Folder 20)
- Carmel, Calif., 25 items (Folder 21)
- Carnegie, Andrew, 1835-1919., 1 item (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Carnes, Henry S., 1 item (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Carnifex Ferry, S. Va., 1 item (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Carpenter, Edward, 1844-1929, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 26)
- Carpinteria, Calif. -- Views., 15 items (Folder 27)
- Carr, Mrs. Jarvis., 2 items (Folder 28)
- Carriages and Carts -- Views., 21 items (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Carrillo Family -- Portrait., 7 items (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Carson City, Nev. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 32)
- Carson, Christopher, 1809-1868., 2 items (Folder 31)
- Cartwright, A. B., 1 item (Folder 33)
- Caruso, Enrico., 2 items (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Casa Grande Ruin., 1 item (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Cashinger, Mrs. Albert, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 36)
- Caspar, Calif. -- Views., 1 item (Folder 37)
- Cast, Dr., 1 item (Folder 38)
- Castella, Calif. -- Views., 2 items (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Castro, Jose, General, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Catepillar Tractors -- Views., 27 items (Folder 41)
- Cather, Willa Sibert, 1873-1947., 2 items (Folder 42)
- Catlin, John - Portrait., 1 item (Folder 43)
- Celis, Eulogio F. De., 3 items (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Cemeteries., 25 items (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Central City, Colo. -- Views., 3 items (Folder 3)
- Chaffee, Adna Romanza, 1842-1914., 1 item (Folder 4)
- Chaikovskii, Petr Il'ich, 1840-1893, -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 6)
- Chandler, Otis - Portrait., 3 items (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Chapman, Alfred Beck, 1829-1915, -- Portrait., 2 items (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Charters, Jonathan., 1 item (Folder 9)
- Chase, H. L., 14 items (Folder 10)
- Chavez Ravine (Los Angeles, Calif.)., 1 item (Folder 12)
- Chavez, Cesar, 1927-1993., 1 item (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Cheyenne, Wyo. -- Views., 2 items (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Chicago -- Views (Century of Progress Exposition, 1933-34)., 1 item (Folder 14)
  ALSO*
- Chicago., 8 items (Folder 13)
  SHELVED ALSO WITH ROLLED PHOTOGRAPHS
- Chicano Movment., 1 item (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Chickamauga, Battle of, 1863., 16 items (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Chico, Calif. -- Views., 31 items (Folder 17)
- Children -- Employment -- Views., 28 items (Folder 19)
- Childs, Orzo W. -- Portrait., 1 item (Folder 18)
- China -- Views., 44 items (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Chinese in California -- Views (Folder 1 of 2)., 26 items (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Chinese in California -- Views (Folder 2 of 2)., 42 items (Folder 22)
- Chinese in California -- Views., 1 item (Folder 5)
- Chinese in Washington (State) -- Views., 15 items (Folder 1)